donnayoung.org 2010-06-21

# Privacy Policy for donnayoung.org

## Privacy

###  [donnayoung.org](http://donnayoung.org/)

## Site-CD (YoungMinds) Customers

#### Customers' Name, Address, and Email 

Paypal will request your name and address for the purpose of fulfilling a site-cd order. Donna Young will receive a copy of the customer's name, address, and email address. Donna Young will keep a copy of a customer's email address, name, and address for the purpose of customer support. Donna Young does not sell or otherwise share any personal information. 

#### Customer's Payment Information 

PayPal will request payment information. Donna Young does not see, have access to, or store any payment information provided by you to purchase a site-cd through Paypal. For more information about PayPal's privacy policy go to: [PayPal's Privacy Document](https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US).

## Donnayoung.org Yahoo Group

Visitors who join the donnayoung update yahoo group will receive an email occasionally usually every two months, more or less. The email addresses are not sold or shared in any way.

## How DonnaYoung.org uses Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. 

Donnayoung.org uses traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our web site in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help me provide you with a better web site, by enabling me to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives me access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. 

## Links to Other Web sites

Our web site contains links to other web sites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other web site. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the web site in question.

## Links to 3rd Party Advertising  

3rd party ads are a common way for web site owners to earn income from their web site. DonnaYoung.org uses "Advertising Affiliate" links. Donna Young is paid a small percentage when a visitor purchases items through the special links. The advertising affiliate links covers the cost of maintaining Donnayoung.org and keeps donnayoung.org from becoming a subscription site. [back to donnayoung.org] 

**Amazon's affiliate advertising program:** DonnaYoung.org is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com or endless.com.

DonnaYoung.org is currently using advertising affiliate links with these online stores. This list is subject to change, so it may or may not be complete. 

## Google Ads

Donnayoung.org uses google ads.

Information about Google's cookies: 
  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
